i did three videos
four videos actually yesterday and many
takes on each of them so even
multiples of that and i want to do an
intro because i'm going to stitch them
together and they're going to be very
long
but i want to tell you why i'm stitching
them together i
have a very mundane life
i live a very specific routine almost
daily
and yet the universe provides exactly
what is meant to happen for me to learn
when i met i'm here to learn
and i think the last 24 hours
showcases that in a mundane profound way
like this is not an exceptional 24 hours
it just so happens i recorded
a video yesterday morning when i was
feeling like crap and feeling like a bad
parent
and i talk about everything that led to
that moment and then i had an amazing
walk in the evening that i wouldn't have
had if those things hadn't happened
and this morning i woke up to a troll
comment on the perfect video that i
needed to watch
and so that's really all you need to
know but if you want to know more about
those three things
then you can watch this entire video and
see
how the universe provides all those
little things
like for instance i was down on myself
in the morning for having attended the
day before
a fourth session of our omega
conversation and then during our walk we
came up with an amazing
uh we were like working out an acronym
in the background while i was on this
other walk and other things were
happening and then this morning
i just sent another one and she just
sent me back this beautiful
new acronym for mlm which is
meta love magic i'm like yeah there's
something
something emerging here and i want to
hopefully inspire people to find this in
your day
during kobit 19 people are so bored and
they're stuck at home
that was my life beforehand but when you
start awakening to what the universe is
giving you
you can learn every lesson like the same
youtube algorithms that make me angry
because it's like you think you know me
and yeah you know what the universe
provides it
the exact right message at the exact
right time including from the trolls
please find the glimmers the triggers
the lessons the universe is giving you
because i guarantee you they're there
thank you please enjoy the three other
videos that i'm gonna stitch after this
one in reverse
i'm gonna give you the troll this
morning
the walk last night and then the
emotional
i feel like a crap person in the morning
it'll be a very long one
and my smoke detector's chirping oh it's
all kinds of perfect
all right take care and the construction
that i was annoyed by yesterday is also
re-happening
and i'm about to go for my walk that i
didn't get to go on yesterday which is
part of the whole story
i woke up this morning to
a trolley i'm fairly sure in his troll
on a comment on one of my old videos
from over a year ago
almost a year sorry and
it was the perfect thing to have happen
as it always is
like it's both because it when someone
comments on it's usually like i'm
reminded that that video exists and i'm
supposed to watch it
and that's enough and it's people making
neutral like neutral comments
or nice comments it's very rarely an
actual troll
but last year i went to
whistler for labor day weekend and it
was the second year in a row that we
went
and on the way up there i had this
epiphany
for a disability league
of um it was something about like people
with different disabilities
empowering each other rather than
relying on outside people to understand
and you know give us charity instead of
solidarity and
and feeling like they're doing us a
favor by accommodating us
because and this is the title of the of
the youtube channel
youtube the thing the episode the
video is um useless eaters it was i was
in the middle of watching
man in the high castle and it's a nazi
concept and the title is something like
useless eaters not what the nazis
thought
and so in the video i talk a little bit
about the disability league around that
time i'm talking about it
and then i talk about how in fact of
course the people
with the um mental and physical
and relief and emotional disabilities
aren't the ones who maybe this guy has
is not um
they're not the ones who are actually
not contributing they're not the act
they're they're absolutely the ones the
nazis
decided to murder for it but they're not
the ones
that are actually taking up resources
are taking and not giving they're giving
a hell of a lot actually
just by existing and um
and yet due to our ableism and society
they're not
able to contribute their gifts they
really aren't
like you're only able to contribute your
gifts as long as you can like fit in
to a able-bodied society
a neuro-diver a neurotypical society
so anyway this guy commented said
something about me being an interesting
creature
and was wondering what i was talking
about and then said something about that
i that this talking creature is a
useless eater
i was like well i eat he's like
and uh i'm saving humanity i'm
anything but useless like by
like a year ago when i did that you
couldn't see
a lot of outside
metrics outside receipts that i was
doing anything
it was all internal right after that and
it's just so anyway it reminds me of
this time it's like a year later copic
19 is happening the world has like
burst into ableism more basically i mean
that's what when it's like oh it's just
people with pre-existing conditions
that's more or less what they're saying
it's just a useless eaters it's all good
it's all good
um it's like don't take away my ball
game oh my god i'd be inconvenienced
do you understand that i'm an important
contributing member of society
no you're not more important than
anybody else anyway so i was
so the fact that reminds me this year
ago we're not able
this family that we went to whistler
with two years in a row we're not able
to
go with this year because i don't know
if they're going they didn't invite us
and also
we're not even able to play days with
them because they're one of the families
that are not taking coca 19 seriously at
all
they're also melaleuca distributors
they're also the mlm people which is my
current like
i don't know what i was talking about is
my special interest the disability
league whether i was talking about
i don't even know what i what i was
talking about when i said that in the
video because my special interests
change under the umbrella of saving the
world finding that out
we're currently right now it's mlms it's
like oh yeah that's what i'm interested
in
is and i have been my whole life like
the math of them and the exponential
growth of like chain letters and stuff
and it's literally what my video two
videos yesterday were about
and so the fact that like it's nearly a
year later it's right before i found
game b it started less than a week
before i found game b
this this um that this video was posted
it's this family that is both
in an mlm or at least was it was a year
ago
they have this weird like i love this
family
my kid plays with their kid and i'm sad
that we can't and i love the wife
and and i love the guy too but
they're like a fake not let's say fake
positivity and
it's that toxic positivity family like
last year when we were
in whistler the girls were walking and i
did this little montage video that an
android will do
and uh the guy was like well you can't
because there was one video of the girls
having basically like
blue steel face like they just look like
they were like
taken over the market like they just but
like in like a
almost [ __ ] way and he was like oh we
can't have that on the internet of her
i was like what like all the other ones
are fine but your
seven-year-old your six-year-old has to
be smiling
has to have every picture be perfect are
you kidding me like that's
that's weird and they are like
constantly i i mean i'm like i'm tired i
can't do that and they're like
when their daughter said that in in
front of me like
she about her own self right it's like
i'm tired and they're like we don't say
things like that and we only we only
talk positive it's like oh god
they put me in the living room instead
of in the bedroom because there was a
couple
and i get it like you of course you put
the single person and
but with a kid like are they really
having sex with their families right
there
i'm the one who needs to wash but they
don't understand they're the people who
think that like
whatever like it was it was if i'd known
i was sleeping in the living room i
wouldn't have went and then i wouldn't
have had an amazing weekend and i
wouldn't have
because it i need to have a place to be
able to go and be
alone and be and it was like constant
the girls
loud and everything else and it reminded
me of that we can run this family at the
mlm the two special interests come
together
that the world right now with it with
its um
with kovid19 and it's bursting at the
seams ableism
and then the two videos that i have
recorded from yesterday that i'm
i'm going to release all three of these
at the same time
and it's like the universe gives you
exactly what you're meant to learn it
was just
that person commented on that video that
what was happening a year ago what's
happening now that it was like around
this family with the mlm and
it's exactly what i'm here to undo that
toxic
positivity that you like this family
just busts it like they
they you know he's he's doing melaleuca
he's oh they their kids in all these
different activities they're trying
i guess they used to have money now they
don't they have to like sell their place
i'm like this is what the toxic
positivity culture does like if you just
think positively enough then
and you'll be successful so if you're
not successful you're doing it wrong and
i
like at their their core they're
personifying that
in a way that's like heartbreaking
and and it's they're learning their
thing that's not really about
i'm gonna redo this one i recorded
several videos this morning but i didn't
post them
because i didn't feel like it at the
time and i wouldn't know the capacity to
post it
but they were explaining that today was
a hard day that i might i had to cancel
my kids play date i feel like a bad
parent
and i will be posting the video now i'll
pick between the three or
maybe i'll weave them together and post
all three that
so i just every morning almost every
morning
i go for a walk and it is my connection
to source
it is how i it's the biggest piece of
self-care i have right now and it's
everything and yet i wasn't able to go
on monday on tuesday because of the
sunburn i got on sunday and i went on
wednesday and then i wasn't able to go
this morning
i know capacity which is partly why i
had to um cancel the play date
partly because my kid also stayed up
till so i shouldn't stay up until 2 a.m
she woke up at 2am and stayed awake and
so
i today was just a hard day for me
she was fine more you know
more or less but like there was
construction on each side
it was driving me crazy and
then she i went grocery shopping to get
some stuff for dinner
i came back and she was passed out on
the table and my kid does not fall
asleep
without like she fell asleep maybe
before she was two years old in the car
seat
sometimes other than that she never fell
asleep when she was eating food never
fell asleep at the table like only in
her bed
and she's just not she hasn't she'd nap
at daycare when she was really young
she's not a sleeper but she's been up
since 2 a.m so she totally fell asleep
so i carried her
as best to my ability to her bed and
she's been sleeping since then
and that was like six she's probably
gonna wake up she's gonna be hungry
and but because she was asleep
i went for my walk i would have went for
this morning
this evening without realizing that it
was getting dark
i went to my usual and i went on the
swings and i was singing to myself the
whole time and the forest was giving me
messages so i also
had some pot which i'm off of at the
moment but i'm letting myself
have on fridays or saturdays today's not
friday or saturday
but there was something about the fact
that i got to go tonight that i was like
no you're supposed to do this
so i did and it wasn't even
like it's not like i have a new fire
that i'm starting that's fully emerged
but it's the same one that's coming up
the mlm one the one around
uh i got the i also did another video
which i may or may not post of me
unboxing the
lmml the essential oils kit that is in
fact an mlm
and i really dislike mlms so i was
watching more of the math on
specifically doterra and i have like
this on my whiteboard because i was i
may still doing a video on
the math of it and how it's broken how
that is like a horrible way
for anyone to make money that isn't in
it from the beginning it's just the math
doesn't make sense but it's a great way
to recruit it's a great way to have
community
it's just not a good way to earn money
because you're the only way you earn
money is off the backs of everyone below
you and you need to basically scam
thousands of people because they're not
going to be able to or if they're able
to
they're going to have to scam people in
order to be able because
the next level won't be able to so at
some level you can't
in any way guarantee that you can
basically guarantee failure
but that's not so i'm going on this walk
stoned i got this oh
like everything that came into what's
emerging right now
the fact of this woman who um i met on
twitter
and is also a world-saving entity we
need a name for it i
i don't know what to call us and
the fact that she got in touch with me
like set off this mlm thing in me that
i've been binge watching
which also the fact like my kid had to
stay up to date
if you have a crap day then had to go
for the walk i had to
listen and actually smoke the pot i had
like there's just like so much that was
happening in that
in that moment that comes into into play
and those are two different things one
of which is
what had to happen to lead to that
moment of me being able to go for that
walk and also what led to
that i'm attending this mlm thing and
i'm currently obsessed with them and
they're currently my special interest
and then while i was gone too um at the
end of our
conversation yesterday which is the one
that i overdid i asked
uh the the two the two women to help me
come up with an
acronym mlm for mlm
that isn't an mlm it's kind of anti-mlm
and i don't remember what she said but
it was it was like multi-level
networking i think and i was like
no because if it's not ml if the acronym
isn't mlm it doesn't um
it doesn't make sense to have it be to
be it's it's
kind of just funny and cute to have it
actually at the academy mlm
and so i remember what i suggested back
but back and forth
while i'm on this walk and in the
background came up with
multi what is not multi was it meta
learning magic which is very our god
that's not a god that's coming up with
the anger group
and that's anyway that's cool then on
the walk i had this
uh because it was getting dark and i
don't normally go out after dark even i
live in a very safe neighborhood
and i'm like in a secluded-y foresty
area not the safest
there's this one i got these these two
image images
just so many messages so many messages
in the forest i saw a rat
and rats are the one animal
that i dislike they're my trigger and
there was something about it but i was
just like yeah
i see you you're not there was no
nervous system reaction i was just like
you're kind of just as cute as a
squirrel
doing your thing definitely scared of
people people are like against them
for just existing um
and then there was this little hole i go
to this walk
every day but i don't go at night and i
don't so i don't go with
dusk yeah dusk
and so there's this beautiful i'm gonna
put on my instagram um
like an entrance to the tree there's
mushrooms growing on either side
and then after i was on the swings
there's this gorgeous
like entryway to the forest when i was a
kid we listened to this
horrible story it's the worst kid story
with these we had these christian
records and they came with like comic
book
like um stories in them one of them was
called nathaniel
nathaniel the grublet they might
actually have it on youtube i'm gonna
link it if they do
and it's about this boy this they're
called grublets and all they do is steal
and so his brothers are like what did
you steal and he doesn't want to steal
so he gets kicked out and goes out to
the forest and he ends up
if you're up the forest after dark you
disappear but it's actually like you're
finding god
anyway so i texted my my two siblings
one of whom i'm not
i mean we're kinda talking but not
really we haven't really dealt with the
fact that we didn't talk for a year and
a half for
and we're just anyway but she texted me
a few times i just like like i don't
wanna hear about book recommendations i
don't wanna hear about your comments on
my health even if it's
trying to help i just don't and yet i
was like okay
there's something about i was just
supposed to like there's some things
only your siblings understand and so i
just texted them like well in the forest
after dark can if
if i disappear just the thang of the
grebline i've sent them the picture
of before us and then i had this
profound sense of
gratitude for this woman who lives in
the community that i haven't been able
to be a part of and she was at the beach
when i got the sunburn on sunday
and she
it's several times like we're not really
good friends she's not
we're not one of each other's favorite
people in cohousing
um but i really love her i think she's a
amazing human being her son's actually
the one who's born
who has shares the birthday with the
with the boy with the the guy whose
necklace i had
the gps coordinate this all like just
ties together anyway but that's not
that's a little bit of a stretch
but anyway and i haven't seen any of
them pandemic and so i saw a few of them
at the beach it was very lonely because
although i was out in nature i was out
in the sun i never do quite well
um they like i couldn't hear because of
the the wind and i didn't realize how
loud it is on the beach it's like
usually a nature i can hear because it's
it's quiet and peaceful and so i
couldn't communicate with them and it
was also like i could
not i didn't want to but just like i
don't want to talk about mundane
i just don't want to talk about even
even about school and the pandemic not
that's mundane but it's like just
tiresome all i want to talk about is
game b all i want to talk about is the
world i want to create
and no one really wants to hear it but i
had mentioned
the um that there's a community starting
in nelson and i'm hoping to find out if
it's possible to move there or start her
own in nelson that whatever whatever it
happens to be
and she called me over to talk about it
like she was like she was like hey come
over here and talk about
tell us about the community and she's
done that several times where it's been
like i've been kind of off in my own
like feeling on the sidelines and she's
just been like
inviting me into her into the
conversation and she's an introvert
she's um like she's not
someone who's overly talkative i
actually am overly talkative but don't
really know how to do small talk and
stuff and she's
kind of the opposite she's like
perfectly comfortable being in silence
her and her her sister and yet i don't
know like just this invitation so i sent
her thank you message that was basically
i don't know if you know you do this but
like thank you i'm very grateful
and listening to those i don't know i
have no idea what's going to come from
either those the message i sent myself
it's like dark i feel like texting
people that i normally i don't i don't
send messages
but listening to the universe when it
tells me to do those little things
getting the message from the universe of
like this rat and this
this little cave and this entryway and
this pathway and like you're on the
right path
and getting to to be on the swings at
the dark and i'm just saying to myself
and getting to experience this because
my kids stayed up till 2 am
and because i cancelled the play day
that made me a bad mom that i felt this
morning
and then i recorded that video so you
can see kind of
that one leading into this i don't know
if people can see what i can see in this
but i want to share these little things
because
like this is where the magic is
happening it is coming together
and it is going to be something that
looks weird as we're going these aren't
youtubey videos but they are
looking back they will be looking back
this will be like
watching elon musk create tesla or
watching oprah
happen and those sound like that sounds
very egotistical it's going to happen
nothing like that because nothing has
happened like this before
this isn't about one person becoming the
focus one person creating stuff it's
about
everyone coming together and creating it
finding the people with the right skills
in the right time
and following the next step and
showcasing that you don't need to hustle
you just need to
be just be you and experience emotions
and learn your your part
and the doing that is its own reward
you don't need to get paid for it you
don't need to like it just all comes
together
and part of it is this mlm thing that's
emerging and
as much as i'm like in judgment over
this woman joining this mlm and like i
even like attend this thing on saturday
it's released because i'm like what if
she
just signed up so that this happened for
me
that sounds egotistical i know to the
outside world but it's not it's like
that's how the universe works
so you can't really judge things because
you don't understand the ripple effects
you don't understand
what comes out of it i could tell you
everything that came into
like like that woman didn't know that
calling me over meant anything to me in
that moment or that she's done that
several times in my life unless i shared
it unless i listened to that inner voice
while i was on the walk to share that
and this wouldn't have been as big if
i don't even know i had construction
here all day
and feeling like
just overwhelmed today oh better world
is on its way
and we all get to participate in
co-creating it together
it's like just around the corner
this is long i don't even care anymore
i'm just gonna do them
okay so i just got the kit
that i'm attending the what i think is
the mlm pitch
on saturday and i just got the kit um
i don't want to show my address or her
address
but this is how much it costs to send me
this
if you're trying to make money at
something having to send out something i
mean i'm in canada and she's in the
states so there's that extra but even if
it's
a couple bucks every time you have
someone attend
okay there's a note here i won't
necessarily look into that
[Music]
try this before class it is it's doterra
essential oils
i haven't said her name right i didn't
do that i wanted to do this on camera
because
i wanted to i don't know get my natural
reaction
but she's sending out that much money to
send out these kits you're never making
money it's one percent
of people that make money at this this
woman is a world changer
a world changer like f the mlm
this woman's changing the world and
she's somehow gotten herself wrapped up
in
an mlm weight management women's health
babies and kids emotional health pet
care
so all the things we care about as women
i mean
the weight management i don't care about
okay it smells lovely i do love me some
essential oils but
okay try this before class enjoy this
sample
uh incredibly powerful yet gentle
anti-inflammatory
to reduce chronic pain and inflammation
take two drops under the tongue
morning and evening for acute and severe
pain take two drops under the tongue as
often as needed an hour
as long as needed i also just watched
the netflix
the there's a netflix series called
unwell
and the first episode is the only one i
watch and it's on essential oils
and talking about there's people who are
like absolutely you should ingest them
this is how we flavor things
uh he was a little bit sketchy even if
he had
millions of followers and then the
people who were like essential oil
actual experts who went to school for it
aromatherapy experts and um they were
like yeah no no you don't ingest
essential oils so i don't know what
so let's just say
there is this that it's not it's
somebody else's name
probably her upline
my dear friend okay
there's a little a little gem here to
hop online and learn about
doterra essential oils can help you and
your family stay healthy i will teach
the class live
using the video conference site zoom
here's what you'll need to know gives me
the account
that's all we're done uh it's this
saturday
at 11 am so basically i'm gonna meet
with the woman who
one woman who i absolutely love who's
you know needs to
needs to we need to figure out how to
get her paid she could do what she's
doing in the world
and then i'm meeting her like literally
hour after hour
it's like one hour at 10 a.m to do the
culture of wii starting with three and
then
i know about this i mean it's a super
cute little bag but it also has no
um cord anyone
anyone branding it's got no branding on
it these little containers
guaranteed i guarantee this package cost
at least twenty dollars to send out
because these little things are if i'm
generous
a dollar for the four of them total and
it's probably more than that
plus the essential oils inside and
essential oils aren't cheap and there's
like
quite a bit in there actually my
diffuser actually just broke i bought a
diffuser from sage
like a decade ago no my child was i
think but i can't remember my child
wasn't born yet or was
i can't remember if i had if it's older
than her younger than her and that's how
i gave to everything
but when i bought it sage made it very
clear that there was a lifetime warranty
and it stopped working like at the
beginning of the pandemic so i haven't i
got to go back into sage now that they
reopened and get a new one
it's also i don't like the look of my
one although it works
the newer ones are much nicer and i
don't know maybe they'll fix it and i'll
have my one back i'd rather that for
environmental reasons but also a new one
it will be will be nice
join with computer audio and join with
videos so we can hear and see you
i know how to assume but not everyone
does
the class is interactive so have your
class packet with you and join
class will last 40 minutes like i
honestly don't know what to do
because she is a person i want to
support i want
all good things for this woman and i in
no way want to support an mlm
especially one that preys on people who
are chronically ill and i know she has
chronic
illness too and i know she's kind of
been doing more of the self-help
getting better and i hope it's from
something else and not just from doterra
but i will go in with a somewhat open
mind no i'm not i can't i can't go into
it with an open mind
but i will go and support her as a woman
i will probably just stay silent during
the class and not necessarily talk about
this stuff
i might mention the netflix uh episode
i hope she hasn't sung too much money
into this
and too much time and energy if she's
doing it just to learn business and just
to learn from
her upline and mentorship i don't think
there's anything wrong with that
but then don't get other people involved
like don't like
other so hard so hard okay i just want
to do that on camera because
i wanted my authentic reaction
and to see maybe i was hoping i'd open
it and be like her own company she was
starting
i mean it is but not in the way that is
legitimate in the world oh but i'm gonna
go smell these essential oils i guess i
could do that
okay thank you but this channel
is mainly meant to showcase my journey
my journey towards creating
my vision into the world and
becoming whoever i need to be to do that
while not trying to become anything
by constantly figuring out who i truly
am and like excavating that
not trying to become
a version of myself that is
palatable to the masses or palatable to
literally anything
anyone else besides myself
and i do i do truly love myself more and
more the more i get to know me
and the more i uncover because i'm
pretty awesome
because everyone's pretty awesome but
there are
that means showcasing the truth the ups
and the downs and today
is kind of a down day i had to cancel my
kid's play date
that she was looking forward to partly
as a consequence
um for for actions yesterday that she
took and
partly for consequences of actions that
i took that
i overdid it yesterday i wasn't able to
fully sleep
we had dental appointment and they took
way too long so we were in the
fluorescent lights and background noise
for over
an hour for anyone else it's not really
a big deal but for me
is i have construction on both sides and
wednesdays is my busy day and i stayed
on
um our omega conversation one session
too long because we get
it's a free zoom account and we get
kicked off every 40 minutes and we go
back in and so we usually go for
three sessions which is two hours and uh
the women on it
ended up coming back for a third which
was amazing conversation like i'm glad i
did it
but at the same time it's like oh it
cost my kid this playdate
as well as her actions and so i have
this like mom shame and mom guilt and my
house is a mess and it's just like
why can't i be a better human being why
can't i
can do what other people can do and then
explaining it explaining it to the other
mom of like i don't have i don't have
the energy
to drive there my kid's been up since 2
am so she's going to be
not not so in a great mood um
and i don't have the energy to drive
there and i definitely don't have the
energy or is it in a time
in the world right now where i can take
transit but then it's like oh can we
reschedule for tomorrow
no i have another thing i have my one
thing going on that day i can't do
like explaining a spoony disability to
anyone
is hard because it's like well you have
the energy to do this video
well not to edit it not uh not to
make it be what i think it should be
i watch all of these people on youtube
who have
amazing channels and a lot of them have
disabilities
uh listening to jessica and i can't even
remember what her channel is called but
she's
she's this beautiful british she looks
like a like put together
50s housewife she's gorgeous and she has
her her wife claudia
and she's deaf and
damn it ipad i'm gonna murder
someone right now
and that like the anger comes out i'm
just like less patience my
thoughts it's like why are ipads so
expensive and their battery sucks and
their plugin doesn't work
and like i just bought a new one because
the other one it's like okay
the world is getting better you are
actively creating a better world
okay yep yep yep feeling
you know i went we went for a playdate
on sunday got sunburned feeling like a
crappy parent because of that then
having to both like
she needs to recover i need to recover
we can't go out in the sun
i needed a couple days and then i wasn't
able to go for my walk in the morning
because i had a sunburn knee and it
hurt to put pants on and
it's just like and then even just like
dwelling on that makes it worse
and it's just it's a show i
don't know what else to say
i'm watching some other person on
youtube who's trying is reading other
people's comments and try not to use
the swear words i'm like oh is that a
thing are we not just wearing on
youtube
because we get shadow band oh oh well
but i just wanna i'm gonna do a video
at some point on this 8080 adhd coach
because she keeps on trickering me
and i find that a blessing like i don't
find the construction on either side of
me trigger we constantly a blessing
although it is like okay this is your
environment you like
my home is my safe space and it can't
really
be a safe space on the days when they're
there and i i constantly keep forgetting
that there's construction
like i was going to do a video when i
got back to my walk yesterday and
outside and i was like right you can't
there's construction on either side you
either have to do it at like six in the
morning
or not at all
but people triggering me like um
including if i start thinking that the
people and i do sometimes i'm like why
are they
there's a pandemic why are you building
houses i'm like right
it's a pandemic people are out of work
these people have jobs
they're providing for their families yes
there's two houses being built to some
degree at least they're happening at the
same time
i can't even tell which side they're
working on it feels to me like they're
taking
oh my god because i can't tell direction
of sound so it's like i can hear it but
is it on this side or the side
no idea no idea at the moment and that
my brain just has to like
a lot of times i'll figure out where
something's coming from i'll find it out
and seek it out so my brain can go okay
it's over there and then i can kind of a
little bit forget about it even if it
can't cancel out the background noise
but it's like right just just pick a
place brain i'm sorry you're not gonna
get to figure out where every hammer
thing is coming from and every every
bang
but today i just feel
like i want to honor that
it's a struggle it's a struggle to
figure out
how many spoons i have in a day and to
not overdo it and every time i overdo it
i get down on myself which gives me less
spoons and then it's like i cut it's a
it's a negative cycle that gets worse
and worse and i know how to get out of
it
i know that that honoring it by by like
swearing when my thing drops and being
like okay maybe that's not the reaction
you quite need not making it wrong for
it
not making me wrong for having it um
just okay but that's not the most
productive use of your
neurological system how can we not get
like not um amp it up not keep it like
you know
and now i'm gonna take apple down i mean
i am i'm totally taking apple down but
not because
their ipad isn't charging and didn't
charge all night that it was plugged in
even though it's brand new and the
cord's brand new and
technology's stupid because it's
destroying our planet like it's not like
this doesn't
although it costs me an actual hundreds
of dollars
it also costs the planet and there's
like slave labor that goes into it
and the fact that it's not a better
product that lasts
for a decade is ridiculous
and yeah i'm gonna swear why because the
world like it's the least of my worries
like are you kidding me someone's
swearing on youtube someone's kid
hearing it
there's much bigger problems and i'm
actually dealing with those problems
both in my personal life i'm gonna read
this video but